CHINEMELUM VICTOR CHINEDUM

CONTACT

- +375 25 769-09-34
- ▼ Г.Гомель, проспект Октября, 46А. "МИТСО" Gomel, Belarus

EDUCATION

2024 - ONGOING Gomel, Belarus
MITSO INTERNATIONAL UNIVERSITY

• Russian language programme

2016 - 2019 Abuja, Nigeria GOVERNMENT SCIENCE AND TECHNICAL COLLEGE

W.A.E.C and N.E.C.O

2013 - 2015 Anambra, Nigeria MATER'S VESSEL SEMINARY OSUMENYI

 Junior Secondary School Certificate

SKILLS

- Marketing
- Coding
- Reading
- Learning New Things
- Collaborative Team Player

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Expert software development professional with proven skills in project management, coding and testing. Brings 4 YEARS+ years of experience in building robust, well-performing applications matching specifications and exceeding expectations. Seeks out opportunities to expand skills and improve designs.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Chims Technology

Software Developer

2019 - 2024 Abuja, Nigeria

- Engaged clients to understand software design requirements and advise on best-fit options.
- Oversaw programming and quality assurance functions for software team.
- Reacted to technical support requests quickly, resolving issues within target timeframes.
- Checked software for errors and coded updates to fix problems.
- · Verified and resolved bug reports and issues.
- Produced clean, error-free code in line with internal quality standards.
- Developed functional web and mobile applications through clean, robust code
- Researched software requirements to overcome potential constraints and produce feasible designs.
- Responded to system faults quickly to minimise disruption to customer experiences.

Vomacc Floodgates Global LTD

Web Designer

2020 - 2022 Abuja, Nigeria

- Worked as part of a 3-person team, and communicated in a professional way
- Managed web pages for data display and entry using appropriate technologies (HTML, PHP and Web CMS (WordPress))

SKILLS

- HTML CSS PHP Laravel Framework Javascript ReactJS
- NodeJS WordPress SQL MongoDB

WEBSITE PORTFOLIO

https://cryptolifedigital.com/

https://sandbp.net/

https://topluxurypeak.com/

http://zoidinc.co.uk/

https://primeprogressng.com/